{
    "id": "4ca073d772444a929f9517f4c281f6a3",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He struggled ……………….. a weighty bag.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "from",
                "of",
                "with",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Deer often come to drink ………………….. the pool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The coronation of the new king was performed …………………… great pomp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The painter will fill those holes ………………….. plaster before painting the walls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The tyrant was pitiless ……………………… his subjects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "towards"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There are several disadvantages …………………………… living alone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She insisted ……………………. coming with us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no point in arguing ……………………… him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you shouting ……………………… me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was mesmerized …………………….. her beauty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "by",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an introvert …………………….. nature.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We could not restrain him …………………. harming himself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}